ONE FOR THE MONEY
yessir
TWO FOR THE SHOW
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO
ON HEADLAND
AND DELOWE
WAS THE START OF
SOMETHING GOOD
WHERE ME AND MY
NIGGA RODE THE MARTA
THROUGH THE HOOD
JUST TRYNA FIND THAT
HOOK-UP
NOW EVERYDAY
WE LOOKED UP
AT THE CEILING
WATCHING CEILING FANS
GO 'ROUND
TRYNA CATCH
THAT FEELING OFF
INSTRUMENTAL
HAD MY PENCIL
AND PLUS MY PAPER
WE CAUGHT THE 86
LITHONIA
HEADED TO DECATUR
WRITING RHYMES
TRYNA FIND OUR SPOT
OFF IN THAT LIGHT
LIGHT OFF IN THAT  SPOT
KNOWIN' THAT
WE COULD ROCK
DOING THE
"HOLE IN THE WALL" CLUBS
THIS SHIT HERE
MUST STOP
LIKE FREEZE
WE MAKING THE
CROWD MOVE
BUT WE NOT
MAKING NO
G'S, AND THAT'S A NO-NO
TWO DOPE NIGGAS IN THE CADILLAC
THEY CALL US
WENT FROM "PLAYER'S BALL" TO "BALLERS"
PUTTING THE SOUTH UP ON THE MAP
IS LIKE "LITTLE ROCK" TO "BANGIN'"
NIGGAS SAID MOTHERFUCK THAT
PLAYIN'
THEY PAYIN'
WE STAYIN'
LAYIN' VOCALS
LOCALES DONE
MADE IT
WITH THEM BIG BOYS
UP IN THIS INDUSTRY
OUTKAST
YEAH, THEM NIGGAS THEY MAKING BIG NOISE
OVER A MILLION SOLD TO THIS DAY
NIGGAS AIN'T TAKE IT LIGHTLY
'96 GON' BE THAT YEAR
THAT ALL Y'ALL PLAYAS HATERS
CAN BITE ME
AROUND THIS BITCH
BACK IN THE DAY WHEN I WAS YOUNGER
HUNGER
LOOKIN' TO FILL ME BELLY WITH THAT "RALLY'S"
BULLSHIT
PULL SHIT
OFF LIKE IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE PULLED
FULL AS A TICK
I WAS STONED LIKE THEM WHITE BOYS
SMOKIN' THEM WHITE GIRLS
BEFORE THEM BLUNTS GOT CRUNK
CHUNKY ASSES
PASSES GETTIN' THROWED LIKE HAIL MARY'S
AND THEY LOOKIN' LIKE HALLE BERRY
SO, SO FINE
INTERTWINED
BUT WE  AIN'T SIPPING WINE
WE'S JUST CHILLIN'
I'M THE RABID VILLAIN
AND I'M SO HIGH
SMOKING FREELY
ME, LIL B
REEK, MONE AND SHUG
AND MY LITTLE BROTHER JAMES
THINGS CHANGED IN THE HOOD
WHERE I LIVE AT
THEM RATS KNOW "MOMMA, I WANT TO SING"
BUT "MOMMA I WANT TO TRICK"
AND "MOMMA, I'M
SUCKING DICKS NOW"
WE MOVIN' ON UP IN THE WORLD LIKE ELEVATORS
ME AND THE CREW, WE
PIMPS LIKE '82
"ME AND YOU" LIKE
"TONY! TONI! TONE!"
LIKE THIS
EAST POINT
AND WE GONE
GOT STOPPED AT THE MALL THE OTHER DAY
HEARD A CALL FROM THE OTHER WAY
THAT I JUST CAME FROM
SOME NIGGA WAS SAYING SOME
TALM'BOUT
NAH, NOT REALLY
BUT HE KEPT
SMILING LIKE A CLOWN
FACIAL EXPRESSION LOOKING SILLY
AND HE KEPT ASKING ME
WHAT KINDA CAR YOU DRIVE?
I KNOW YOU PAID
I KNOW Y'ALL GOT BEAUCOUP OF HOES
FROM ALL THEM SONGS
THAT Y'ALL DONE MADE
AND I REPLIED THAT I'D BEEN
GOING THROUGH
THE SAME THING
THAT HE HAS
TRUE, I'VE GOT MORE FANS
THAN THE AVERAGE MAN
BUT NOT ENOUGH LOOT TO LAST ME
TO THE END OF THE WEEK
I LIVE BY THE BEAT
LIKE YOU LIVE
CHECK TO CHECK
IF IT DON'T
MOVE YOUR FEET
THEN I DON'T EAT
SO WE LIKE NECK TO NECK
YES, WE DONE
COME A LONG WAY
LIKE THEM SLIM-ASS CIGARETTES
FROM VIRGINIA
THIS AIN'T GON' STOP
SO WE JUST GON' CONTINUE
ME AND  YOU
YO MAMA
AND YOUR COUSIN
TOO
ROLLIN' DOWN THE STRIP
ON VOGUES
COMIN' UP
SLAMMIN'
CADILLAC
DOORS